Anna: Pete, hi! Hi, we are here!
Pete: Hi, Anna! Hi, Marsha!
Anna: Hi!
Pete: How are you two?
Marsha: I am great!
Anna: You know, Pete, I am new to D.C. The city is big.
Pete: Yeah. But you learn a little more every day. How's the new apartment?
Anna: The new apartment is great! Let's get coffee!
Marsha: Anna, do you have a pen?
Anna: Yes. I have a pen in my bag.
Anna: I have a …
Pete: It is not a pen. It is a book. It is a big book.
Anna: Yes. Yes it is, Pete. I know I have a pen, though…
Anna: I have a ....
Marsha: It is not a pen, Anna ... a toy?
Pete: And it is a pillow!
Anna: Pete, Marsha, I know I have a pen.
Marsha: Anna, it is a map.
Pete: Why do you have a map of the world?
Anna: Pete, Marsha. Now I know I have a pen.
Pete: And now you have a lamp.
Marsha: Anna.
Anna: I have a pen! Let’s get coffee!